(Sheldon:)It bothers me.
(Howard:)-Sheldon, this is a summons.
-A summons? For what?
Looks like you ran a red light...
...on Marengo Avenue at 9:30 p.m.
on November 16th.
They got you on a traffic camera.
Nice picture.
November 16th? Penny, that's
the evening you fell in your bathtub.
(Sheldon:)I had to drive you
to the emergency room.
(Penny:)No, it isn't.
(Sheldon:)-Yes, it is.
-No, it isn't.
I have an eidetic memory. That's
a picture of you in the passenger seat...
(Sheldon:)...holding your dislocated shoulder.
Hmm. No, it isn't.
(Sheldon:)Okay, then why is a summons
for a traffic violation...
(Sheldon:)...committed in your car, bearing
your license plates, coming to me?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
(Penny:)Okay, look, they sent me the ticket.
(Penny:)I told them I wasn't driving,
and they were all, "Who was it?"